

Miroslav Krsmanovic

web designer / junior dev





in ∂ (devfolio d'

Junior Web Developer with one year of experience in building web apps mainly as a playground for learning new skills. Seeking an opportunity to extend my knowledge and implement solutions to meet business needs. Currently learning Angular 2+. I'm familiar with basic concepts.

Experience

Freelancer.com

2015-2019

Creating brands for various businesses.

UpWork.com

2015-2019

Web design and web development. Using WordPress as a primary technology for building simple web sites.

Greco

2019-present

UI/UX designer responsible for creating an intuitive, user-friendly web app. Developing wireframes and user journeys based on research and testing.

Education

Faculty of Security Studies

2009-2014

Univeristy of Belgrade. Bachelor degree

IT Academy

2017

Web desgin department. Getting familiar with basics principles

Computer School Vinca

2018

PHP and MySQL web application development

Computer School Vinca

2018

Course of WordPress. Theoretical and practical examination